In this section, I'm going to give you another
Nesta seo, vou dar outro
challenging exercise. So open up the Mocking folder,
exerccio desafiador. Ento, abra a pasta
and look at this file. HouseKeeperHelper.
Mocking e veja este arquivo. HouseKeeperHelper
In this class we have a public
Nesta classe, temos um
static method called SendStatementEmails.
mtodo esttico pblico chamado SendStatementEmails.
The job of this method is to get a bunch of house keepers of the
O trabalho deste mtodo  obter um monte de detentores de
database. For each housekeeper it's going to generate a
casa do banco de dados. Para cada governanta, ele ir gerar um
statement file and save it on the disc, and then it will eventually
arquivo de instruo e salv-lo no disco e, em seguida, ele enviar por e-mail
email that statement file to the housekeeper. So this is the
esse arquivo de instruo para a governanta. Ento esta
big picture. Now if you look at the implementation of this class you can see
a grande figura. Agora, se voc observar a
these two methods, EmailFile and SaveStatement, they are both
implementao dessa classe, poder ver esses dois mtodos, EmailFile e
private methods. As I told you before, look
SaveStatement, ambos so mtodos privados. Como eu disse antes, veja a mesma afirmao
it's the same statement and you can see it's a private statement. So as I told you
e voc pode ver que  uma declarao privada. Ento, como eu disse
before, you should not test these private methods, they are
antes, voc no deve testar esses mtodos privados,
implementation details. And here we have EmailFile again
eles so detalhes de implementao. E aqui temos EmailFile
private static void. And the rest of the code in this file
novamente vazio esttico privado. E o resto do
are just simple stubs I've generated to make this code
cdigo neste arquivo so apenas stubs simples que eu
compile. Because one of my students sent me the source code
criei para compilar este cdigo. Como um dos meus alunos me enviou
and I didn't have the entire code, so I had to reverse engineer it,
o cdigo-fonte e eu no tinha o cdigo inteiro, tive que fazer engenharia reversa
and generate some classes to make the code compile. So don't worry about
e gerar algumas classes para compilar o cdigo. Ento no se preocupe
any of this stuff here. Your job is to write
com nada disso aqui. Seu trabalho  escrever
all the required unit tests for this method, Send
todos os testes de unidade necessrios para este
StatementEmails. Now before you get started I want to give you a couple of
mtodo, Enviar e-mails de declarao. Agora, antes de comear, quero
things (?). These two methods, SaveStatement
dar-lhe algumas coisas (? ). Esses dois
and EmailFile, they both touch external
mtodos, SaveStatement e EmailFile, tocam recursos
resources, so don't get stuck looking at the implementation of these
externos, portanto, no fique atento
methods. You need to extract these methods, put them in separate classes,
implementao desses mtodos. Voc precisa extrair esses mtodos,
and then use dependency injection to inject those dependencies
coloc-los em classes separadas e, em seguida, usar a injeo de
inside this housekeeper helper class.
dependncia para injetar essas dependncias dentro dessa classe auxiliar de governanta.
So, I want you to pause the video, and use what you have learned in this course
Ento, quero que voc pause o vdeo e use o que aprendeu neste curso para escrever todos
to write all the required unit tests for this class. Next, we're going to look
os testes de unidade necessrios para essa classe. Em seguida,
at my solution.
vamos ver minha soluo.